[{"answer": "-- who wants to come forward.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 27, "question": "What did I say?", "qSentId": 26}, {"answer": "I did, and I'm very sorry about that.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Did you call me Anderson, John?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 74, "question": "You know, that behavior with the reporters earlier, you'd never see a conventional politician talking to them like that, and yet that is part of Herman Cain's charm, isn't it?", "qSentId": 73}, {"answer": "Well, I think it's quite likely.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "How likely from a legal point of view is that, do you think?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "Well, I would say more specifically that the GOP voters are not put off by these allegations because they went through the sexual harassment whiplash of the '90s, of the Anita Hill accusations against Clarence Thomas, then the Paula Jones accusations against President Clinton, where we saw a lot of feminists, you know, frankly, changing their tune when it came with sexual harassment.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 111, "question": "What do you make of that?", "qSentId": 110}, {"answer": "Well, it tells me two things.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "What does that tell you about the nature of these allegations?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "Well, I haven't seen a racist undertone to this.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "What do you think of the central charge that there is a racist undertone to the way that people are now going after Herman Cain?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "ERSHOWITZ: Yes, I think there's an enormous difference, no matter how despicable you might think that Edwards was, it was entirely voluntary.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Alan, you want to jump in there?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, in the case involving Thomas -- not in terms of veracity, but in terms of whether there's any racism involved.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Why would that make any difference in terms of the veracity of the allegations?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I think he does if it's not quid pro quo sexual harassment.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Alan?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "I think it's far too early to tell, but I would say that Herman Cain should have given Mike Murphy a call, and he was the GOP strategist who had Arnold Schwarzenegger say, where there's smoke, there's fire.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 163, "question": "OK, Amy?", "qSentId": 162}, {"answer": "Well, I don't -- I don't actually know him, but this is what our primary season is all about.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "But what do you think of him personally?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "Well, I actually don't like playing the race card on either side.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 207, "question": "When you see the charge of potential racism in the Herman Cain case, people saying that people are only going after him because he's a black conservative, do you think that holds any merit?", "qSentId": 206}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think you can read anything in at this point.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 220, "question": "What can you read into this from your experience?", "qSentId": 219}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Which of the candidates do you find yourself agreeing with most on their policy statements?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "No, I certainly don't get itchy fingers about throwing my own hat in the ring.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "Do you think maybe you should throw your hat in the ring, albeit, belatedly?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, there was the relief that I finally finished the writing, which, as you know, can be quite trying.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What did you conclude about that period in your life?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "Let's start over.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "How have I done there?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 317, "question": "Object of affection?", "qSentId": 316}, {"answer": "Well, revolutions are not pretty, and there are any number of circumstances in which the tyrant who stays too long and refuses to leave and when fear breaks down, and on behalf of his people, and the tables are turned, those ends are often very violent.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Well, the circumstances were fundamentally different, and the times were fundamentally different.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 333, "question": "Do you look at what's happened to Barack and Gadhafi, and slightly regret the way you helped the administration go about Iraq?", "qSentId": 332}, {"answer": "ICE: I'm really a policy person.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 374, "question": "Is that a total lifetime pass, or could you see yourself tempted back?", "qSentId": 373}, {"answer": "Piers, that's a no.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "You're not entirely ruling it out?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Well, I actually had a couple of people with me traveling with me.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "Who was the first person you told when you heard the news?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "Well, of course, it was a wonderful experience, and it was a very high honor, as I said.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "So I guess mixed feelings?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Well, clearly, associating the United States of America firmly with the freedom agenda in the Middle East after 60 years of trying to trade democracy for stability and getting neither, I'm very proud of that speech in Cairo in June of 2005 that set a different tone based on President Bush's second inaugural.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "And very quickly, if I was to pin you down and say your biggest triumph in the eight years and your biggest regret, what would you say?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "I -- somebody has to be in charge.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 449, "question": "You're the god mother?", "qSentId": 448}, {"answer": "Mom.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 456, "question": "What's the most important role you have?", "qSentId": 455}, {"answer": "Kardashian chaos, so it's going to be everything, anything Kardashian.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "It's all happening in Vegas, right?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "Is it always sells this Kardashian stuff?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 500, "question": "What's the weirdest stuff that you got in there?", "qSentId": 499}, {"answer": "Yes, don't tell me that.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "It's on the rocks?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "Yes, as far as I know.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Still happily married?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "Honestly, we had a show kind of in the works and had a tape done before that happened.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "How much of your brand -- and I'm playing slightly devil's advocate here, but how much of it could have been possibly without the explosion of attention that came with the sex tape involving Kim?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Well, that came first.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 543, "question": "Did you think, there goes the show, well, there goes my daughter?", "qSentId": 542}, {"answer": "Um, Kim told me.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "How did you hear about this tape?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "My girls and my son, their hearts, they are good people.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "What are you proudest of with your family, would you say?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "Kim.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 576, "question": "Who?", "qSentId": 575}, {"answer": "Yes, it's lovely.", "docId": "111102pmt", "aSentId": 581, "question": "Will you tweet it to me?", "qSentId": 580}]